comeet.co 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Comeet -– Comeet –

Comeet Technologies Inc. (“​ **Comeet** ​”,  “​ **us** ​”, “​ **our** ​” or “​ **we** ​”) provides a solution for the management of employment candidates' information and communicating with candidates for employment (the “ **Solution** ​”). Comeet respects your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how Comeet uses data and information provided to Comeet through the Solution or while visiting our site located at ​ **app.comeet.co** (the “ **Site** ​”).

“​ **You** ​” includes:

  * “ **Customers** ”: these are organizations, and employees, personnel or representatives of organizations, which have subscribed to use the Solution including for the purpose of employing candidates;  and
  *  “ **Candidates** ”: these are (a) candidates for employment, who communicate with Customers or transmit information to Customers by means of the Solution or (b) potential candidates for employment whose information is publicly available or obtained by Customers other than by means of the Solution, and input by Customers to the Solution.

​If not otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms have the meaning given to them in the Comeet Terms of Use, which are available ​[here](http://support.comeet.co/terms-of-service/)​ (the “ **Terms** ​”).

In this Privacy Policy, when we use the term “​ **Identifying Information,** ​” we mean information that can be directly associated with a specific individual or entity.  Examples of Identifying Information include, without limitation:

  * name, address, telephone number or e-mail address,
  * information about activities directly linked to an individual, such as the employment or educational history of a specific individual,
  * observations that a Customer may make in respect of a potential employee, including during an interview, or
  * information regarding hiring decisions made by such Customer.

Our Solution is a service tool used by our Customers to manage information about prospective employees and communicate with prospective employees.  Our Customers are solely responsible for ensuring that their use of the Solution complies with applicable laws and does not violate third party rights. We do not control what information our Customers input in the Solution, or how our Customers use your Identifying Information (as defined below) and we are not responsible for such use. If you have a question regarding how a Customer uses your Identifying Information, please contact the relevant Customer. When we receive Identifying Information in connection with potential employment with a specific Customer we _do not_ share such Indentifying Information with other Customers.

**Information We Collect**

We collect some information on behalf of our Customers, and some information for our use, all as described below.

**Information collected on behalf of our Customers:**

  * When Customers, such as potential employers, recruiters or manpower agencies, use the Solution to collect, use or store data of or communicate with potential employees, they input Identifying Information relating to potential Candidates in the Solution.
  * Candidates may also input their Identifying Information in the Solution when they apply for employment for our Customers or communicate with our Customers by means of our Solution, including by way of Customers’ websites, on our Site, by means of third party job boards, by emails or other means.
  * Customers may also input certain Identifying Information regarding potential Candidates whose information is publicly available or obtained by Customers other than by means of the Solution. This information may include the Candidate’s name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, employment or educational history and other information.

**Information collected on our behalf:**

  * Customers that register to use our Solution will be required to provide us with certain Identifying Information.
  * If a Customer or Candidate signs up to receive emails or updates about our services, they will provide their name and e-mail address.
  * We also collect any Identifying Information contained in any message that you may send to Comeet.
  * The Solution may gather information regarding the system and browsing activity of Customers and Candidates that access or use the Solution or visit the Site, including information regarding Customers' or Candidates' operating system, browser and IP address, how a Customers or Candidate interacted with the Solution, or activities performed by Customers or Candidates using the Solution.

You are not legally required to provide us with Identifying Information.  However, if you do not provide such information you will not be able to register for, transmit information by means of, or otherwise use our Solution.

**How we Protect Information**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Identifying Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Identifying Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Only authorized employees or authorized subcontractors of Comeet have access to our production infrastructure, and passwords Customers provide us are strictly regulated. We limit access to Customer data to a select few employees [or authorized subcontractors] who need it to provide support and troubleshooting on our Customers’ behalf. Accessing data center information as well as Customer data is done on an as-needed basis or to provide support and maintenance.

**How we Use Information**

Our Solution is a service tool used by our Customers to manage information about prospective employees and communicate with prospective employees. Identifying Information provided to, on behalf of, or in connection with, a specific Customer will be accessed and used by such Customer and its representatives. We allow representatives of Customers to access the Identifying Information which they inputted or which was inputted by Candidates in connection with a position with such Customer.

Our Customers are solely responsible for ensuring that their use of the Solution complies with applicable laws and does not violate third party rights. We do not control how our Customers use your Identifying Information, including by means of the Solution, and we are not responsible for such use. If you have a question regarding how a Customer uses your Identifying Information, please contact the relevant Customer.

When we receive Identifying Information in connection with potential employment with a specific Customer, we _do not_ share such Indentifying Information with other Customers.

Except as expressly set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share Identifying Information with third parties without the express permission of the individual identified in such information and the Customer (if relevant).

We may use Identifying Information internally – for example, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to make Comeet more useful, to customize Comeet and personalize its content.

We may use Candidates’ Identifying Information in order to send notifications on behalf of the relevant Customers with respect to the employment process.

We may use Customers' Identifying Information to send Customers information regarding the Solution.

We may share your Identifying Information with:

  * Members of our corporate family, or third party vendors or service providers, such as email service providers sending emails on our behalf. We may also authorize third party vendors or service providers to collect information on our behalf, provided however that any collection or use of information by such third party vendors or service providers shall only by done in connection with the regular operation of our Solution or for the delivering of services to our Customers. Do not worry, we will not share your Identifying Information with such third party vendors or service providers in connection with other business endeavors.
  * Referring websites. If you were referred to this Site from another site (for example, through a link), we may share some information about you with that referring website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any website that referred you here. Additionally, when you link to one of our partners from our Site and/or Solution, we provide that partner with a unique identifier so they know that you were referred from our Site and/or Solution. This unique identifier will not contain any of your Identifying Information.

In addition, by analyzing all information we receive, including all information concerning use of the Solution and the browsing habits of end user of websites that incorporate the Solution, we may compile anonymous statistical information (“​ **Statistical Information** ​”). Statistical Information helps understand trends and customer needs.

Statistical Information is anonymous and we will not link Statistical Information to any Identifying Information. We may share such Statistical Information with our partners, without restriction, on commercial terms that we can determine in our sole discretion.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to a visitor’s browser. The browser provides this piece of text to the device of the originating visitor when this visitor returns. Comeet uses cookies to help personalize your Comeet experience. A “persistent” cookie may be used to help save your settings and customizations across site visits. Also, if you log in to Comeet, such a cookie will be used to recognize you as a valid user so you will not need to log in each time you use Comeet. Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but you can change this setting so your browser either refuses all cookies or informs you when a cookie is being sent. Also, you are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. Please note that some features of Comeet may not function properly when cookies are disabled or removed.

**Online Links to Other Sites**

You can link to other websites of third parties that provide useful information/services. Any Identifying Information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to this third party and is subject to this third party’s provider’s privacy policy. We advise you check these privacy policies. We do not have access to the information collected by those third party websites or by our partners. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party websites to which we or our partners link.

**Use of Comeet by Children**

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 14. In the event you become aware that somebody under the age of 14 has enrolled without parental permission, please inform us immediately. Potential employers, recruiters or manpower agencies may not provide information with respect to potential employees under the age of 14.

**Third Parties**

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy only describes the policies of Comeet. Comeet does not control how Customers and/or entities using the Solution may make use Candidates’ information, including any Identifying Information. Comeet shall have no responsibility or liability for the collection, use or storage of any data by any other entity, including without limitation any Customer or potential or actual employer making use of the Solution. Candidates should not provide any information to any entity unless they are comfortable with the privacy policies of such entity.

**Correcting or Updating your Information**

We provide the Solution as a service to our Customers. If you have provided Identifying Information to a Customer by means of the Solution, for example, in applying for a position, please contact such Customer with any questions or requests regarding your Identifying Information. We allow Customers to view the information they provided during registration or when uploading potential employee’s data and to alter any data, inaccuracies or errors. We also allow Candidates and Customers to view the information they provided when requesting to receive emails from us to alter any data, inaccuracies or errors. To request such access, or correct, update, or amend your Identifying Information please contact us at the following e-mail address, postal address or telephone number:

E-mail address: [info@comeet.co](mailto:info@comeet.co)

Postal Address: 550 S. California Ave, Palo Alto

Telephone number: 650-433-9027

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us at the e-mail address, postal address, or telephone number listed above. We will retain Candidates’ data in a manner consistent with our obligations to our Customers. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Communications**

We may use Candidates’ Identifying Information in order to send notifications or communications on behalf of the relevant Customers in connection with Customers' use of the Solution.  We may send Candidates and Customers email or other messages about us or our products and services. By accepting the Terms of Service (including the terms of this Privacy Policy which are incorporated therein) or using the Solution, you affirmatively consent to receive such commercial messages. You can ask to have your Identifying Information removed from our mailing list and stop receiving future commercial messages from us by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at info@comeet.co. You will also be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from commercial messages in any such email or other message we send. However, please note that we reserve the right to send you service related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages, relating either to your account or to your transactions using the Solution, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them unless you cancel your account.

**Other Uses or Transfer of Your Information**

We will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities, regulatory or government bodies, or court order requesting or directing us to disclose any information, including Identifying Information. We may use subcontractors that are located in countries other than your own, and send them information we receive. For example, we may send your information to the United States or to countries outside the United States or the European Economic Area. All our subcontractors will be subject to nondisclosure and non-use obligations. Nevertheless, some countries may have levels of protection of personal and other information which are not as high as in your country of residence or business.

We may transfer our databases containing your Identifying Information if we sell our business or part of it.

**Changes**

Comeet may update this Privacy Policy from time to time – we encourage you to review it periodically.

**Comments and Questions**

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at info@comeet.co.

Last updated: December 2015  
Version: 1
